That's this odd facade
Yeah, let the pixels glow, let the pixels glow
These words are truth in drag
Paint it wrongs that never lack
Who does he think he is?
They type, better aim your curses right
Dance with go
This panel
Who's love not me I'm shadow band again
Pro Mutual Mike then boom
Drop a baseline dirtier than the check
Smashing routers like vows, Canada dries, licking watch catalogs somehow.
Rando's ranting bout A.I. Toons, while his playlists saw cartoons.
Mason's pacing red outrage, threatening people from an undisclosed stage.
Natalie Benz's back foot behind head, mods praying Lord, not again.
And from the bone, brags he just dropped a cosmic load
Alex and his mic, nuclear loud, beat the storms and turn it down, you clown
Tony bombs the stream with skin, chat explodes, mods dive in
He manning time, roguin' free, burnin' bridges, livin' HD
Authors there just smiling sweet, y'all need Jesus or at least some sleep
And it's all so true.
Ghost is connected.
Canada drive timed out.
Randall's still typing.
Wait, did Vita just ban me?
Laughter static cat me out.
End stream no.
Yeah, I should have room bands.
Oh, I did.
Watch this.
This isn't my transformation.
Talk about shapeshift to her watches.
Presses.
Almost as good as a woman putting on a band on my head almost
Okay, let's see
Hi everybody. Hey Barbara Chanel same in NYC stacks. How are you guys? We're just starting out the night
Thank you Chanel look at my everybody, I'm not gonna do too much music, but
It's been five minutes.
I'm just reading a really interesting story right now
about somebody named Harley.
Hold on a second, I'll be right back.
I'll be bigger, hold on.
Harley past her neck.
Has anyone heard of Harley past her neck?
There's a story.
I'll read it to you.
You can actually pull it up too.
It's still up.
Okay.
Talk about a trainer.
Listen to this.
I remember this story from a couple years ago, 2023.
Working for the military is an MK Ultra trainer
stalking Kanye West.
Working for the military, I wasn't governed by the same laws
as a typical person was, so I could look at the impact
of certain drugs that are not everyday things, okay.
Slobbery gossip outlets have been a buzz
over a run in between famed rapper Kanye West
and his former personal trainer Harley Pasternak
in Dubai, a hotel earlier this month.
According to West, Pasternak has been following him in Dubai, a year after West leaked purported
texts where Pasternak threatened to have him institutionalized.
Pasternak, for his part, has reportedly claimed it was actually West during the stalking at
the Dubai Hotel.
Why does any of this matter?
Because Pasternak has connections to the CIA's MK Ultramind Control experiments, leading
to some to believe that he may be a psychiatric handler for Hollywood stars and other celebrities.
Wes posted screenshots of text from Pastor Knack last November where the trainer allegedly said he could have you institutionalized again
Where they can medicate the crap out of you and you can go back his zombie land forever
Play date with the kids just won't be the same
This shows Harley admitting to knowing the truth of our origin but then later dismissing the facts within the same text chain
Wes said mind you
This is how a Hollywood trainer speaks to a far more influential black celebrity when we get out of line
It turned out Pastor Knack may have indeed
have the power to institutionalize West. Indeed, Pasternak's prior employer, Canada's Department
of Natural Defense, is the same agency that once participated in the CIA's Ultra Mind Control
experiments. A video of Pasternak talking about his work also resurfaced around the time of West
Controversy.
Working for the military, I wasn't governed by the same laws as the typical person was,
so I could look at the impact of certain drugs that are not everyday things,
Pastor Neck said. In June, Pastor Neck was also spotlighted for his connections to
transgender celebrity Elliot Page. At the time, Page revealed that the decision to undergo a
sex change came after having a psychotic episode and hearing a voice in her head.
One night he tried to knock himself out took his knuckles to a space and counted over and over till bruises formed for today
After he sat down in a lawn chair in the porch ashamed his face or the LA Times were on pages transition using the same male pronouns
That page now goes by and then he heard a voice. You don't have to feel this way
Okay, the Hollywood trainers gets publicly addressed speculation. It's interesting
Canadian military are being used as MK ultra trainers for
Celebrities in America. I mean, it's not too far-fetched. I don't think okay. I didn't share it, but here
I'm gonna share it. Okay
You do remember that yeah
It's an interesting up your personal trainer
Can take Canadian mind control expert?
interesting
It's just I didn't
And the Canadians have special Canadian military a special
Special ability to test on on psychiatric drugs or something
Interesting
It's just I
Do you remember that from a few years ago, right and everyone's like, oh, that's just like to that's so I know that doesn't happen
Hollywood, that's all
It's all conspiracy theories, right?
They'll also keep Halle Berry's personal trainer. We think a personal trainer wouldn't have that much, you know
Military intelligence background, but I'm just going to personal training, but I mean he is a Hollywood personal trainer, right?
L is weird and so is Canada, but
How are you guys doing I don't have yeah, I have a couple copies
I've been like just drained though
Tonight what else do I have?
This is a McDonald's item. Maybe not everyone knows about
You seen this one?
Slicing snack wrap
Yeah
They're kind of like a McDonald's style pita
You know you can a deal I
Know I've good Canadian people
Here
But you have MK ultra trainers the thing that is page Canada dry
Interesting choices for me
A little bit obvious, but I
Love oh, okay, remember the song oh Canada you are Chanel
Chanel Chanel how much experience you have in the Canadian military? It is one thing that is how much
Come on. What what what level is warlock? I want to get to the warlock part
The page is a witch, you know, literal witches and warlocks.
I don't...
I...
Come on, you kept to give me...
Tell me about your time in the Canadian military, guys.
I'm just kidding.
I hope I'm just kidding.
I need to do a Canadian video besides the ones I have.
I mean, it's the closest I can get right now.
Next to the biscuit, here we go.
He's a thinker from a frost and pine
Head shines bright, got a reasoned mind
He'll test your words, he'll twist your view
But he'll smile when he knows he's got through to you
Think that is steady as stone
Mind in the core, sharp as a flame, fair as the wind that carries his name.
From Canada's hush to the world's loud room, he stands his ground, clears the gloom.
He'll question your gods.
At the end of the fight
Think that it's steady as stone
Argus the stars, but never alone
Generous heart, never cruel heart
I see the brave kind of gentle that lets others be free
Think God is bold and bold
Warm in the cold worth more than gold
He fights for the fair
To the man who
I guess we could start with how Harley-Pastronik publicly represents himself.
How do we even get here?
Yeah, well, we are looking into the web of Hollywood lies.
We are starting to realize that if you're in Hollywood, you probably shouldn't have
a gym trainer or a bodyguard, because a lot of people just seem to be with them when they
are in their last moments of life or found floating in bathtubs, that's all I'm saying.
who have been found in that regard.
I mean, Brittany Murphy, her husband as well,
rather notoriously, Mack Miller, Harley-Pastronik spoke out.
I was just about to meet with him.
I can't believe this happened.
It's weird.
And then of course, notorious,
threatening text messages to Kanye West,
which put him on our radar in the first place.
So I started looking into Harley-Pastronik
and he's definitely someone that I would say is
proud of his heritage, so proud that what initially flagged me as weird was him holding
up an unclear image of his grandmother, this image, so far away, that's allegedly Lucy
Pasternak, who he claims was a survivor of the Holocaust, not only just a survivor of
the Holocaust, but was in the worst camp, Auschwitz.
And it says, this is a photo of my late grandmother Lucy
Pasternik.
She was from Transylvania and survived Auschwitz.
A great deal of who I am today is because of who she was.
And he has this adorable little girl holding up the photo,
but it's not a close shot.
And I just was not able to confirm that.
It struck me as odd that I could not confirm that.
Care Essentials breaks the cycle with potent natural oils
that combat resistant fungus at its source.
Our blend of lavender.
Tea tree and almond oils restores thing. Don't wait. Click the link in the
Speaking of his celeb clients, I just wanna know no one knows and
No one knows, no, no, no, no gym trainer, no one knows any gym trainer that texts you and threatens to institutionalize you and
Take you away from your kids that formerly worked for the military
Speaking of his celeb clients. I just showing you some on his website here
That's a lot of people to be training at the gym everyone from one of Paltrow to Kim Kardashian Kate 80 Perry
Man, what's this guy's gym routine for someone with military training?
I mean literally we could scroll forever and you could just see how many A-listers he
Manages at the gym some who I
Can't imagine have that great of a workout routine and it really does make you wonder why we are always getting the same things said out of Hollywood.
but there are some clients that have always struck me as odd, you know, but Harley-Passionate has
also had a lot of clients who have died, you know, in strange circumstances. Brittany Murphy,
do you remember her? She died back in 2009, collapsed in the bathroom of her phone,
you know, of her home and she was found unconscious. She was then transported to the hospital. She was
extremely young when she died. The autopsy results say that she died of pneumonia and iron deficiency.
Okay, Pastor Nick claimed that Brittany's husband,
who then died shortly thereafter as well,
had hired him to work with Brittany Murphy.
So that's interesting.
Then Mack Miller, I don't know if you remember,
the 26 year old rapper who died also
of an accidental drug overdose.
Pastor Nick had told page six
that he was just about to see Miller.
Miller was just about to walk into his studio
on the day that he died.
And then there's Aaron Carter to connect the dots with you, because this one has always
bothered me the most. On the very day that Kanye West tweeted out Harley-Pastor Nick's tweets,
Aaron Carter responded to Kanye West. You can see that date on November 3rd,
They never had the opportunity to talk because less than 48 hours later, Aaron Carter was
found dead.
He died at his home in Lancaster, California, at the age of 34, and his body was found in
a bathtub by his housekeeper and the LA County Medical Examiner's Coroner.
And you guys know if you're reading chaos that what they rule these deaths means absolutely
He drowned after he wanted to speak to Kanye West about the Harvey
Wines, about the Harvey Pasternick text messages. Harley, Pasternick, pardon me.
Quite stunning stuff, quite amazing stuff. So I wanted to share that with you because it has
bothered me spiritually.
that people continue to attack Kanye
and to attack him and to call him crazy
without listening to his version of events
that he has told many times.
And now I'd like to draw your attention
to Harley-Pasternik's 2019 interview
that he gave to Escape Fitness
discussing his military training
and the impact of drugs for the military.
Take a listen.
And the area that I was interested in
was how drugs and food affect muscular performance.
And when you say drugs without like performance in enhancing drugs or they all kinds of drugs, right?
Okay, so working for the military
I wasn't governed by the same laws that the typical person was so I could look at the impact of certain drugs that are not that are not
Every day things so we looked at a drug called midaphanel, which was for narcoleptics
So if you give a soldier this
drug
How long could they stay awake for?
detriment.
Is that used now as one of these brain drugs?
I've heard the name before somewhere.
Yeah, so it's a very interesting medaffinil.
It will keep you awake, but it's not a stimulant.
So if a special forces person has to stay awake for three nights waiting for the right
opportunity to do whatever they have to do, we could give them a medaffinil and we'd
So if you want to know who I believe is a monster at Harley-Passion it would be that individual and as I said, I think that yay barely escaped with his life.
Know the story and so I've never seen that um that video before my surprise Aaron Carter shows up in that
No, I surprised
No, did I know no
Just a coincidence just a coincidence
And led to certain things at certain times and then that pops in just a coincidence of
That's a coincidence. Yeah, he shared the text. He shared the text from his personal trainer telling him that the personal trainer is like
I'm gonna have you I can have institutionalized, but you on drugs-centered zombie land
Your business with your kids won't be the same
Interesting for a personal trainer to say
Anyway
And then I get tired then I get a wave of Blake
Go to sleep go to sleep go to sleep go to sleep
30 minutes, I will at 30 minutes you have 20 seconds left. Oh
My god, what are you eating? What are you eating? Oh?
Lola don't eat that. Oh, okay. She brought in a wrap
She's just like, Lola, no, no, no!
Well, Psyche's in his speedo. Stars and stripes parade. Fish tacos on the table. Another wild charade.
He's hitting on the straight men. Come on, lose that shirt. Meanwhile, Vita's on the hotline. Yell until it hurts.
Pretty pages dodging simps. Like dodgeball in the gym.
Man of the dry got gonged off, didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marcy flashing, chaos on the feet
And here comes a porn bomb, oh lord
Sting's with Fuzzy Bear
Arthur's stirring pots
Like he's cooking up a scare
Truckerado rumbles in
Sammons chasing views
DJ Electra's cartoon face
Is breaking all the rules
On too far, we've turned the trolls into our own mim.
Welcome to the show, where every wild night becomes another in...